

I'm passionate about technology, science, developing things that improve people's lives and make the world a better place. I've been working with mobile development for iOS platform since 2014 with experience on all steps of iOS development, from the concept ofthe ideas until releasing the app on the store and following the results with analytics, tests and crashreports.

# **EXPERIENCE**

FREELANCER IOS DEVELOPER **FREECAST INC**Since January 2021, Working with Swift for iOS and tvOS applications

IOS DEVELOPER ▼ PAGSEGURO UOL

July 2018 - March 2021, Working with native applications using Swift

FREELANCER IOS DEVELOPER ♥ STORMBREAKER STUDIOS

January 2020 - December 2020, Working in iOS applications using Swift

IOS DEVELOPER **▼ BRQ** 

April 2017 - June 2018, Working with native applications using Swift and Objective-C

IOS DEVELOPER ▼ MAGNA SISTEMAS

February 2016 - April 2017, Working with native applications using Swift...

## **EDUCATION**

## SYSTEM ANALYSIS AND DEVELOPMENT

Learning algorithms, software engineer, databases, software development in FMU, Sao Paulo, Brazil

#### **IOS DEVELOPER**

Learning a lot of concepts about iOS development in Impacta, Sao Paulo, Brazil

#### **SKILLS**

- > Xcode
- > Obj-C
- > MVVM
- > (|
- > SPM
- > Auto Layout
- > Framework Building

- > Swift
- > git
- > MVC
- cocoapods
- > Tests
- > Agile Methodologies